Hi, my name is Nicole Wilson
and I'm the director
of admissions here at River Ridge Living Center.
We are conveniently located in the south side of Amsterdam.
Nestled in a quiet,
tranquil setting on well manicured private grounds.
When you first enter our facility, you'll be greeted
by our warm and friendly staff and be welcomed into the warm
and cozy ambiance of our beautiful lobby.
We have both private
and semi-private room options available each
with its own restroom, flat screen TV,
and storage space to make all our residents feel comfortable
and at home while they're with us.
This is our rehabilitation gym.
We are proud to offer therapy services, including pt, ot,
and Speech open seven days a week.
We are very proud of the success our rehab team has
consistently shown as an extremely important piece
of the healing journey.
Here at RiverRidge,
we have a beautiful dining room where our residents can come
to eat, relax, and enjoy spectacular
recreational activities.
Our dietary department caters
to our residents specific dietary needs and diets.
Our sunroom is a place our residents come to relax
and visit with their family and friends.
And it wouldn't be unusual to see deer
and other wildlife passing through during your stay with us.
Thank you for joining me on this virtual
tour of River Ridge.
We look forward to having the opportunity to assist you
or your loved ones with their rehabilitative journey.